numerology.com 2018-08-22

# Tarot.com's Privacy Policy

Effective January 17, 2017; Last Updated: July 17, 2018

Tarot.com may gather information for the following reasons:

### Introduction

This Privacy Statement applies to the websites owned and operated by Daily Insight Group, a subsidiary of Zappallas, Inc., ("Daily Insight", "we", "our", or "us"), including Tarot.com, [Numerology.com](https://www.numerology.com/), [Dailyhoroscope.com](https://www.dailyhoroscope.com/), [Twittascope.com](https://www.twittascope.com/) and [Dailyinsightgroup.com](https://www.dailyinsightgroup.com/). This Privacy Statement not only applies to our websites but also Daily Insight’s applications and services that collect personal data and display these terms (collectively the "Platforms"). This Privacy Statement does not apply to any Daily Insight Platforms that do not display or link to this statement or that contains its own privacy statement.

Daily Insight is committed to protecting your privacy in a number of ways including using industry accepted security measures to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of data in our systems. This statement is designed to describe how we secure and maintain your personal data when you visit our Platforms or when your personal data is collected during your use of the Platforms. Rest assured, your personal data will never be sold, rented, traded, shared or leased other than as outlined in this Privacy Statement. 

Daily Insight does not publish text, images, or multimedia content that portray nudity, foul language, violence or other data not suitable for children. Our Platforms are not directed to children under the age of 13. Where we discover that personal information of an individual under 13 has been provided to us, we will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from our systems. 13. We are committed to complying with applicable privacy laws and adhering to appropriate measures to ensure security of personal data.

### Collection And Use Of Data

**_Data Collection From You_**

**Data You Provide Us.** We collect data directly from you when you register for our Platforms, personalize your account or pay for services or products through our Platforms. For instance, when you create an account with us you may be required to provide a name, email address and birthdate in order for us to provide you with products and services through our Platforms. In addition, to provide you with a more individualized experience, like a personalized horoscope, astrology, tarot or numerology report, you may wish to provide your birth location, zip code, astrological sign, gender, and other related data. Where you choose to purchase products or services, including Karma Coins® tokens, gift certificates and expert readings, we will collect credit card (and PayPal) data such as credit card numbers, expiration date and billing address, but this data is sent directly to our payment processors and is never stored or otherwise retained by Daily Insight.

**Data We Automatically Collect.** When you interact with our Platforms we may collect data about you through automated means such as your mobile phone number, unique device ID, device type, machine ID, geolocation data, computer and connection data, browser type, IP address, domain name, and date and time stamps for your visits. We may also collect data associated with your use of our Platforms, including data about the way you interact with our Platforms or any content or advertising included on our Platforms, your page views and traffic to and from our Platforms, hyperlinks clicked, and the URL you visited before and after you use the Platforms. As is the case with most websites, we also employ cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and similar technologies within our Platforms to collect and store certain data about users, to improve our Platforms and advertising, and to help us remember you and your preferences when you revisit our Platforms. Please see our Cookie Policy for more information about what we automatically collect from you.

**Data Collected by Third Parties.** We may incorporate third party ads, offerings, and other technologies (such as plugins, pixels, and cookies) into our Platforms, enabling third parties to collect usage, demographic, and other data (including personal data) about you and your online activities through your use of our Platforms and across other websites and applications. Any data collected through such integrated ads or technologies is collected directly by those third parties for use and disclosure and is subject to the third party's privacy policies. Please see our  Cookie Policy for more information about third party cookies. 

**Data Provided to Social Networking Sites.** Some of our Platforms may offer you the ability to connect to your social networking accounts (“SNS”) such as Twitter or other social networking sites directly from our Platforms to the SNS or from the SNS to our Platforms. Where you choose to connect your account with a SNS we may receive or access data about you from the SNS if you post or otherwise share data on the SNS connected to your account. Please remember that any data you post to an SNS will be accessible by any users of the SNS and subject to the SNS's terms of service and privacy policy. 

**_How We Use Your Data_**

We use your data to provide you with products and services including fulfilling orders (including process payment), responding to inquiries or customer service requests, administering your account, and displaying content based upon your interests. In addition, we may use your data to market our products, Platforms, promotions, and offers which we feel you may find interesting, provided you have not opted out of receiving such data or, where required by law, we have your express consent. We may also use your data to understand general customer trends and patterns and improve our Platforms.

**_How We Share Your Data_**

**Third Party Service Providers.** We may disclose your personal data to third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf including third parties that process payments; send marketing communications on our behalf; help us create or maintain our databases or help us research or analyze use of our Platforms. We require our service providers get your prior consent to use your data to market their own products or services to you directly. When we transfer any of your personal data to a service provider, the provider will be contractually required to use your data only to carry out the services we have requested, to provide appropriate protection of your data and to comply with applicable laws and regulations.

**Third Party Partners.** We may share data with our third party partners including advertising partners. When we do, we will either aggregate (combine the data of numerous people together so that the data does not identify you) or de-identify (remove or change data to prevent association with you) your personal data so that the third party will not be able to associate that data to you, your computer, or your device. 

**SNSs and Third Parties Using Integrated Technology.** As discussed above, data collected about you via third party ads, SNSs connected to your account, and other third party integrated technologies (such as plugins, pixels, and cookies) is collected directly by, and therefore disclosed to, the third party or SNS. Any such data is subject to the third party or SNSs privacy policy. Please see our Cookie Policy for more data about what we automatically collect from you.

**To Comply with Legal Process.** In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us.

**Third Parties to a Business Transaction.** In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal data will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Platforms for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal data.

Where we want to share data with third parties not described above, we will obtain your consent to do so.

### Storing And Accessing Your Data

**_How We Store And Secure Your Data_**

Daily Insight will take appropriate precautions to protect personal data in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We are committed to complying with applicable privacy laws and adhering to appropriate measures to ensure security of personal data. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**_Updating Or Making Choices About Your Data_**

If your personal data changes or if you no longer desire to use our Platforms, you may correct, update, or delete data about you by logging into your account profile on the applicable Service and making changes within your account settings. You may also email us or contact us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days of receiving the request.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to have your Twitter® or other SNS account linked to your Platforms account, you must de-link the SNS by logging into your profile for such SNS and changing your preferences. Please refer to the privacy settings of the SNS to determine how to adjust our permissions and manage the interactivity between our Platforms and your social media account.

You can choose to stop receiving personalized emails, promotional emails and newsletters from us at any time simply by following the email preference link at the bottom of any email or newsletter, or by logging into your profile on the applicable Platform and changing your account preferences. Please note that in order to continue servicing your account, you may not opt out of receiving non-promotional emails regarding your account or your transactions with us.

We will retain your data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide the Platforms. We will retain and use your data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Do Not Track Signals

At this time, our Platforms do not support "Do Not Track" preferences that may be available in your browser. For more information about Do Not Track, visit [donottrack.us](https://www.eff.org/issues/do-not-track).

### Linked Websites

Our Platforms may contain links to other websites that are not covered by this statement and where data practices may be different from ours. If you submit personal data to any of those sites, your data is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

### Additional Disclosures For Users Based in the European Union

The European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation and other data protection laws grant you certain rights in relation to your personal data. Where applicable to you, you can:

• request access to your personal data and how we process it   

• request correction of the personal data that we hold about you  

• ask us to delete your personal data   

• object to us processing your personal data   

• request the restriction of processing of your personal data   

• request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party   

• withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data.

Note that withdrawing your consent to our processing of your data will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. You should also be aware that if you do withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain Platforms to you. Where this is the case, we will let you know at the time you withdraw your consent. Please note that even after you have withdrawn your consent we may be able to continue to process your personal data to the extent required or otherwise permitted by law, in particular in connection with exercising and defending our legal rights or meeting our legal and regulatory obligations. 

Please also note that in some cases, as we have previously noted within this Privacy Statement, you are able to access, correct and update your personal data directly by logging into your account. Should you need additional assistance, please contact us by [email](mailto:support@tarot.com).

### Changes To This Privacy Statement

Any updates or changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted to this Privacy Statement, and across our Platforms including out websites' home pages, on our app, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice as described in this paragraph, prior to the change becoming effective.

### Where To Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact us at: 

Daily Insight Group  
7412 SW Beaverton Hillsdale Hwy, Suite 102  
Portland, Oregon 97225
